♪♪
And we are back. GM GM.
Yes, hello.
How are you doing?
I'm doing good. How are you?
Yeah, I'm busy.
Like, I need more agents to do more agent stuff.
How many agents do you have running?
So right now I have 10 different walkthroughs
working on the side and grok boats.
And I'm getting limited because I reached my limits --
monthly limit, end-weekly limit.
QSO increased the usage,
and then my grok boats used it all, you know, so...
But how many boats do you have active to just reach the limit?
QA stuff, some content.
I have a CTO. I have a CO.
Yeah, no, it's --
I mean, I'm not reaching the grok boat limit.
I'm reaching the QSO usage for the grok boats
to use the models.
Yes, that makes sense.
Yeah, the other one.
And, yeah, I spent, like, two, three days.
When we had the Super Grok EV subscription,
and then I used QSO to just, like, discover it again,
yeah, I'm on it.
So it went away fast.
That goes fast, yeah.
Yeah, yep.
But, yeah, what about you?
Yeah, well, I'm trying grok boats.
I've been testing it the last week, and I'm really happy.
Yeah, thanks, Elan.
Yes.
We've made our lives so much easier.
Subscribe to the livestream, Elan.
We love you.
I am not -- First, I tried.
I said, "Okay, check this every hour."
And then it doesn't work.
It forgets checking. It hangs.
And, you know, if you have a check in Outlook account,
it goes to the web version,
and every time it checks, it opens a new tab.
Oh, yeah. So eventually, the browser on their PC
that the bot is using will be so slow
that he just stops doing the tasks.
Yeah, they have some small VMs, like, behind grok boats, right?
Like, it's not the biggest resource ever.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
So right now, I set up a Slack.
I didn't use Slack anymore.
I switched to Discord, but I did set up the Slack right now,
and every webhook from something that's triggering
is going to Slack, and that notifies the bot,
and then the bot checks it.
So everything is real-time.
And did you use cloud Slack
so you can use your cloud on Slack?
No, I didn't use a cloud. I used a grok bot.
Yeah, but, like, you can connect cloud to your Slack instance,
so you can use it, like, directly,
and you can -- If you hired people,
but you don't because of the agents,
if you have a team, the whole team can build,
"Hey, cloud, build that," blah, blah, blah.
Yeah. I don't know.
I was watching the video about the grok bot team,
and they were telling about trust compared to the usage.
I don't know if I trust the grok bot.
Yeah. Yeah.
Also, in the answers, I've asked it to --
Every time I get a ticket in my support system,
I said, "Okay, read the ticket, read the history,
see what we can reply, and create a concept
and send the concept to me so I can give feedback to you
before you send it."
I don't trust it that good yet.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's going good for two days, and on day three,
it feels like it's back to the Stone Age,
and it's stupid again.
Oh, it has some open-claw PTSD.
Yeah. So I don't know if it makes a different decision
or if it has less memory that it can use.
I don't know.
I think memory is still an issue with AI agents.
Like, from one week to another, like, they forget the whole,
"Read this file," blah, blah, blah.
Again, every session, blah, blah, blah.
Like, it's not stable yet.
And on request features, please, fix the memory.
Less memory to your Starship, more memory to the AI.
Yeah. By the way, do you use the 1 million context
and even, like, the upcoming, like,
2 million context windows stuff?
No. I don't know how it is now, but a few weeks ago,
everybody said it will make your model worse.
Yeah. So I disabled it.
Yeah, me, too. Okay. I'm on the 200.
Yeah. But also, models will become more expensive
if you use them higher memory or the higher --
the 1 million amount.
Yeah, because there is more cache to cache,
like, more context to cache, so then it's --
because it's getting stuck in each session,
so then it compounds all together.
Yeah. But also, I was checking the API.
Maybe we can check it here.
I was asking Grok about Grok 4.6 API costs,
and because I was comparing it,
and it should be cheaper than Sonnet.
Okay. But the catch is, if you use up to 300,000 tokens,
it's, like, the next amount of sense,
but if you go above it, it doubles the pricing.
Ah.
I think a bigger prompt doubles the pricing,
and I couldn't find it here,
but Grok found it somewhere for me.
I don't know if it's...
Okay. $2 million, $2 million, cache, input, context, API beer.
Let me see if I can find where it was.
Oh, yeah. No, that's a bench, and I'm --
Okay.
Really? Yeah.
Oh, and what's the Grok build?
'Cause...
Everybody is using it to build websites and stuff,
and I tried it, but I was not happy,
so I didn't try it anymore.
But Grok build is not the terminal?
No, no, no. It's in grok.com.
Okay. On the website.
You see it as an option.
Okay.
Ah, here it is.
Let me check.
I will send you the URL.
The URL.
Okay. You have it.
That should be the one.
This one?
Yeah, you see it. Short contacts, long contacts.
Oh. Okay.
And when they send you the e-mail
that they updated the pricing and made it cheaper,
it only shows the cost for the short contacts,
but if your contacts is bigger,
you'll get a double in pricing, and then it's expensive.
That's -- Okay. Fair enough.
Yeah, and you see long contacts,
and Grok 4.6 is above 200K tokens.
Damn.
Oh, yeah, like 200K.
Yes.
So if you're building something and you have an API call,
you probably want to optimize it because if you just say,
"Hey, I sent everything because it's cheap,"
well, it just doubled in price.
Ah, it's only for the API?
Yeah, I couldn't find it on the other ones.
Let me check if Grok knows this as well.
Because I was comparing it, and Fable said to me,
"Hey, yeah, you're right.
It's cheaper," and then I put it into Grok,
and Grok just said, "No, no, no.
It's not cheaper. Only on small contacts there."
Okay, so, Evan, Fable lied to you.
Is Fable still lying that way?
It couldn't find it, or it just read it off.
Okay. Oh, yeah.
That's why I still think that important stuff,
you need to double-check between AIs.
Yeah, for real, like the review everything.
I don't trust anyone. It's true.
Okay, but you know what's cheaper than Grok 4.6?
Paying nothing at all.
Exactly. Free model on open router, man.
Okay, let's go.
Get Grok, get open AI.
Yeah. We have something better.
Exactly. All of that is garbage.
Put that on the side because it's too expensive.
I refuse to pay for my AI now.
Yes, and it's not only for good developers,
it's for everybody.
Yeah, exactly.
Because, okay, so last week,
Grok opened, yes, that's pretty.
Last week, open router announced the 0x alpha
was in stealth mode, okay, like the launcher model,
and they are going to get your prompt
and see if you like it and then launch it a week after,
which now they are announced that this model
is from ZAI, and it's GLM 5.3.
So during -- wait.
Yes, during a few days,
everyone was expecting analyzing the token output.
Okay, wait. Let me...
Zoom in.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Okay, yes. Thank you.
0x alpha unmasked.
Okay, cool. I'm going to talk about that.
That would be better. Cool.
So, yeah, now that we know that 0x alpha is Z.AI GLM 5.3 flash,
and during the full week,
everyone was trying to guess based on the input,
the output of the model, et cetera,
like which model it was.
It basically lasted like 15 minutes.
Like, everyone was already talking about GLM 5.3.
Like, yeah, just after the launch.
And for a week, like 42 trillion tokens in six days,
yeah, open code, and it's seven, way more for open router.
Yeah, six trillion tokens for open router,
and how much I said for open code?
Where is it?
Yeah, 42 trillion tokens for open code.
Okay, back.
And, yeah, that's a big lunch.
And it was good. Did you try it or not?
I didn't try it.
Yeah.
It could have been like a billion more.
Yeah, you still have one day, I think, to try it.
I didn't find any crazy, big mistake stuff
because even like the benchmark was like --
in some benchmark, it was on pair with Fable 5.
And for free.
And we had that for free for a week.
Yeah.
But I had some issues try testing the model.
In open code, sometimes it just like stopped working.
I was not able to see the results in the station.
It's just like, "Build, build, build.
Stop building. What's happening?
Oh, I was building. Build, build, build.
It stopped again."
Yeah, well, on the free one, so many people are using it,
probably spikes in the usage,
and then it just goes out of a connection or something.
Yeah, exactly.
So that was a bit annoying.
And if you want to, like, do some work stuff,
that was not the best way of, like, putting the features.
But on some small scope,
or Evan ordered the GitHub dashboard and stuff,
that was pretty interesting.
Okay, so basically that --
Okay, now I'm going to do that. Yeah.
And because of that stealth month,
I decided, like, to retry open code.
And, Evan, you can do that on Curso by changing the API keys.
So you can bring your open router key to Curso
to use the Curso interface to use free models.
And Evan, like, retried open code because it was a CLI,
and it was, like, working the best with,
like, this stealth month --
this stealth model.
And, yeah, now I've discovered even more free models
because I like to pay, but, yeah,
if you can get those free models for free, that's even better.
-Then why not? -Yeah, for real.
And, basically, if you --
Like, free models are getting even better and better.
Like, for example, you have Muse 1.2 from Facebook,
so you can even test it for free.
That's cool.
And I would say it's more intelligent
than all of the models that we had before with OpenClo, right?
So you can just use free AI, no?
-Yeah. Well, you need Curso,
but you don't need a subscription to change it,
or do you put in your own API?
-I don't think so because it's using your --
Okay, so -- -It's using the API,
and you just get the software, so that's it.
-Yes.
So you have a nice UI to use AI, basically.
-Yeah. -But, okay, maybe.
I'm not going to show my key.
Let me check before models, API keys.
Yes, it's not displaying it.
Okay, cool. So I can show it.
Tag, tag, replay.
Ah. Place, window, Curso.
Okay.
So if you go to settings and models,
so you need to change the override of open AI key
and the endpoint,
and it will work to change to open router.
-Cool. That's cool.
-I mean, it's cool. It's a bit tricky.
UI stuff, you just need to know it.
But then you can use those free models.
That's lit.
Okay, so if I do that, if I do that.
On this Mac, I want --
Oh, yeah, I open code, but, okay, let me --
Tag on this Mac, open folder.
Tag, ship, ship, show.
Open router three, open.
Nice. Let's get back to it.
Window, Curso, path.
So, now, I'm in Curso.
I'm in open router three.
I have the model connected.
Hello? Who are you? Thank you.
Plan ending suit.
No. No, I don't want to resubscribe to --
I have a Super Grok subscription.
-Yeah, maybe just update on the bottom left.
-Yes, let me just use it.
But, yeah, OX Alpha, AI Coding Assistant, blah, blah.
Directly into Curso.
It's cool.
And, yeah, that's open, a new world of possibilities.
But, okay, so, also, what I want to show was tag,
open router, path.
So, that was open router, but, no, open router two.
I don't want this to it.
I want this to it.
So, open code, and, basically, yeah, that's the --
That's one of the first state I guess they did a try.
-To see if it isn't a Chinese AI or another one.
-And I guess that's working.
-Yeah.
-Tag, yeah, see, 21st of August.
ZAI is compute constraint.
Kimi 2 is not quen.
Minimax, Xami -- Ah, okay, so, this one was wrong.
Minimax, Xami, trust me, 100%.
Okay, trust me, but it's wrong.
This is not a Chinese model.
It is a Chinese model.
It says a GLM next model of Xami MIMO V3 on the August 21st.
So, yeah, like, some people got it right away.
And that's kind of smart because for the launch,
that also creates some engagement
because everyone is speculating, right?
-Yes, and people will test it.
Even if they don't know how open router works,
they will test it after when it's live.
-I mean, it works for me, right?
I never spend the time to try out
all of those free-model stuff.
I never, like, use open code, et cetera.
So, yeah, it works for me, too.
-And it shows why Cursor, again, is a perfect product.
-Yeah, I mean, like, it's become really, really great.
I mean, I guess with $60 billion, you can have some nice --
-You can do it a lot.
Well, I had Cursor before, and I removed it from the PC
because I didn't like it.
And now I installed it with my Grok Super Heavy.
-Yeah. -And I'm using it again
because it's cool.
-And because you don't read the code anymore.
Oh, at least the pull request.
-Less. -Yeah.
But, yeah, we don't need the IDE anymore, right?
Because you can just ship features, review them,
review them on GitHub, but also, like, on Cursor,
you can also review the PR directly into Cursor.
They have the PR review view.
So, yeah, it's a big win for Cursor, for sure.
-And you can also just ask Grok to connect to Cloud
and ask Fable to test everything, to get feedback,
and that works perfect, as well.
-Oh, so you have Grokbot connecting to your Fable 5?
-Yeah. -And test --
Ah, interesting.
Okay.
-It just does it in the terminal and in Cursor.
It works perfectly, and it gets the same feedback
as when I ask Cloud myself, so...
-Yeah, because, yeah, it's via the CLI,
so it's the same, right? -Yeah.
-Okay, I just want to check if they talk about GLM 5.
Maybe we'll have it later.
Um...
Tag, tag, GLM 5.0.
Okay.
So, Max.
Released August.
Okay, fair enough.
Speed.
Okay, whatever.
Pricing.
I want chat.
No, I don't want to click on ZAI.
Model comparison, okay.
Intelligence 9.
Ooh.
-That's good.
-Okay.
So, that means we had a top-ten model for free for a week.
-For a full week.
And everybody was screaming when they got Fable
for the first week where you could just do tests
and they could build everything.
Well, imagine what you could have built
and what you lost in a week.
-Yeah.
-Because you didn't use it.
-I mean, you didn't use it.
-Ah, yeah, I know.
But sometimes I have so many agents running.
-Yeah. -I need to understand it myself.
Or I need to trust my agents that everything is going okay.
-I mean, okay, so, yeah, I mean, like,
if you have, like, 50 sessions open at the same time,
you still need the bandwidth to check them
and read what they say, right?
-Yeah, we need a new MacBook or the new Mac Mini.
-Yeah, or even, like, the new MacBook Pro,
what, like, 10 grand?
The Anytime Ultra?
Okay, so, I just want -- Okay, so, five.
Fable 5 with fallback.
What?
Okay, then, okay, that's nuts.
4.6i, genome 5.3, speed.
It's not that crazy fast.
Oh, okay, no, no, no, okay, no.
Let me -- No, it's fast.
It's faster.
Wait, it's faster than Grok?
-Yeah, and why is Grok so low?
-Because, um...
-Oh, it's a 4.6.
4.6 is slower than 4.5.
-Yes, yes, yes, but, okay, so, Gemini 3.7 flash,
which is normal, then.
Oh, maybe that's good.
For identical conversation, maybe it's fine.
It's good.
But 90 TPS compared to 57 on Grok.
Okay, that's interesting.
But the curve per task, same.
Okay.
Okay, no, it's even cheaper than Grok.
Okay, that looks a good model, huh?
Damn.
Do you have a ZAI subscription?
-Nope. I failed.
-Yeah, I mean, oh, yeah, because they closed it, right?
It was Minimax. I don't remember.
-No, they closed the other one, the Kimi.
-Yeah, Kimi was closed, right, but not ZAI.
Okay, so, okay, I guess it will come here after.
So, yeah, 60, right?
So, here.
Okay, fair enough.
That was a good model for free.
And now I'm going to, yeah, keep following the timeline,
and when there is a next Delft mod, I'm going to be there.
-And if you want to be, as well,
just follow Shipjet on next, and we will share it.
Back, and I think that's all I wanted to talk about
about announcing all of that.
It's official now, ZAI official release, blah, blah, blah.
Yeah, we're good.
The new model that swept to the top online usage charts
with high performance at zero cost was created by China.
ZAI, also known as Zippo, nice, swept to the top
by giving away for free with no limits.
-Yeah. -Yeah.
-Imagine how many data centers are running to get --
to make the free possible.
-Yeah, I mean, like, the compute was bit like --
for example, for Kioso, slash basics, right?
I don't feel that they are still fighting for compute anymore.
You know what I mean?
It looks like even they build too much compute
for the usage, so it's not the exponential of usage
that everyone is expecting anymore, so.
-They also optimize models constantly.
-Yeah. True that.
Okay, cool.
Okay, so I think we can jump to the demonstration
and what we build because it has been 30 minutes already.
Tag, tag, tag, tag, tag.
Okay, so.
So, what can we build with those little free models?
I want to try them.
I want to try them now by building a YouTube transcript,
so we drop a link, we give a link, we get the transcript,
and if it will build that correctly,
then I want to have the clip,
so it will cut the clip of the best moment
that we have doing a live stream.
-Okay, so, basically, at the end of this video,
we can drop the URL in,
and it will create all the clips for us.
-That's what I hope it will build with a free model.
-With a free model. -With a free model, yes.
-And in 30 minutes. -Yes, exactly.
-Let's go. -So, let's go,
because that's a challenge.
Tag, path, so, okay.
I'm going to change that.
Replace window.
Or maybe I should use cursor.
That would be better than open.
Yeah, okay.
Yes, open free, so.
Okay, I'm going to close this session,
and I'm going to open a work tree.
New work initial.
Fuck.
New folder, 0xalpha, and --
Oh, no.
Git, ignite the repo, and create two folders.
0xalpha and muse.
Okay.
I should have done that, but, yeah, whatever.
So, yeah, we're going to build the app twice,
or at least we're going to compare,
like, which model will perform the best,
and I'm going to do that.
And, oh, I didn't --
Okay, so maybe I will keep those replaced,
because I have them on open root,
so I didn't think about late night.
Where is my --
Where is it?
Okay, cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, nice.
So, I have muse on the left,
and 0xalpha on the right.
And I want to use the prompt.
So, we are building a small standalone TypeScript tool
called YouTube Distiller.
Paste a YouTube link,
and you get back what the video actually said,
plus a handful of moments worth watching,
cut, and playable, et cetera, et cetera.
I want to edit that.
I'm going to put that here.
So, a prompt of 46 lines,
and create it in the folder 0xalpha.
I'm going to read that after.
That creates it in the muse folder,
because I want to compare against 0xalpha output.
So, yeah, read-only, do not write code yet.
It has two faces of one engine.
It runs the full state below,
and emits progress even when it goes.
CLI, server.
The UI is a simple, static HTML file.
No React, no Bundler, whatever.
Pipeline.
YouTube downloads.
Download the video in the English auto-caption
in GZone 3.
Parse the GZone 3, one request to open router,
free route with the entire transcript.
FM peg cuts the rank moment into playable file,
zero model request.
Runtime, minimax, free.
Okay, file off.
Tech, always.
Hi.
Fuck.
Confirm.
Okay.
Cut the rank.
I didn't check that it's using the runtime model,
so I'm not going to do it.
Oh, yeah, no, it's a backup,
because I asked for a backup of the model
if Muse is not working.
-Ah, cool.
It's not Muse.
-Yes, so runtime model.
-That comparison failed fast.
Keep Muse for execution,
because it's working.
Tech, what did I do?
I'm going to -- Fuck.
What?
Just end it, bro.
We use model, runtime model.
Keep Xerox Alpha, because it's working.
So it looks like Xerox Alpha is way faster than Muse,
or maybe it's --
-What I like to do is, when it has the full MD ready,
I say convert it to HTML so I can read it easier
and open in the browser,
and it gives you the full plan of HTML.
-Okay, so give me the plan in HTML
so I can read it better.
Tech of tech.
-Yes.
-Okay, okay.
Okay, cue, cue, cue.
Okay, cool.
I just want to check the artificial analysis
between Muse, Muse 4.1, right?
That's Muse 5.2.
I think it's the old one.
Replace Muse.
Okay. Wait.
Is that the -- Oh, August.
Okay, okay, okay.
So that's nice.
I haven't -- Jesus.
Even this model is, like, cool.
Okay, so, for example, like, a Muse pack,
I selected from open code free selection,
and the OX Alpha is on open router.
Like, back, replace, window, open router.
Okay, the document is building.
Okay.
Open.
Open the files.
Oh.
Tech.
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
Nice.
Path.
Tech.
I'm gonna -- Okay.
So that's the plane for Muse.
Replace YouTube distiller.
Bam.
There it is.
One engine applying two faces CLI plus SCC.
SCC?
Ship-shit easier.
Yeah?
Well, it will probably explain it when we read further.
SCC.
No, it doesn't.
No.
SCC, SCC, server, SCC endpoint.
What?
Whatever.
So, free tier environment.
Okay.
Oh, that's the add constraint.
20 request mean, one request --
Oh, yeah, yeah, because there is a limitation
in the open router in the free model.
Like, so, if you pay 10 bucks to open router,
then you have one request per --
1,000 requests per day.
And if you don't have money at all, then it's just 20.
So it has a difference.
But you can pay 10 bucks to have, like, 1,000 requests.
Anyway, that's fine.
Okay, so file layout, watch fill out zone,
blah, blah, blah, page.
Okay, so we have both.
The server, YouTube transcript, LLM open router, whatever.
Clip, counter, server, and public,
which is, like, the static page.
Model ID, fallback models.
Nice.
Exact JSON parsing approach.
Okay, so then, yeah, then I have the time.
I have the -- for the subtitle, the transcript.
Single requests, JSON schema, nice.
Okay, so then I have the transcript.
Cool, cool, cool.
Validation and what happened on malform output.
We don't need to handle errors. Everything will be perfect.
-We just push it. -Yeah, exactly.
Failure handling, nice.
Request counter, user always see budget used.
Okay, cool.
Progress event shape, oh, CLI and SCC consume it.
CLI download.
Oh, okay, okay.
So, SCC, whatever.
So, we are going to have the CLI where download via the clip down.
Okay, cool, nice.
MPP cut line for 90 minutes live build.
Projects cut folding, 10 minutes.
Okay, let's see how it goes.
Total 90 minutes.
We don't have time, bro.
We don't have that time.
-Do it faster. -Yeah.
Path, okay.
So, that looks legit.
I mean, if it works, right, like, so it goes.
And that's from, yeah, GLM 5.3.
It's the same plan, man.
Keep budget, blah, blah, blah, building.
That's a bit shorter, but that looks legit.
I want that.
Yeah, maybe we can just say do the steps
that can be done within 30 minutes
so that we can see the first things.
Yep, path, path, window, path.
So, proceed, but don't spend 30 minutes
to build, skip, end-to-end test.
You have five minutes.
-Yeah. -Thank you.
It will be cool if we can just build everything in five minutes.
Yeah.
Open your browser, model not keeping the max free
as a primary model in a one-line swap
if it ever degrades or whatever.
Cool.
Okay, and I think I will need the open router key,
so I'm going to get one keys.
Where is it?
Sign up.
I don't want to sign up. I want to sign in.
Okay.
Path.
Oh.
Okay, so looks like the MUSE one just went straight for it.
Tech, workspace, profile, API keys, shape sheet, show.
Okay, expiration, one hour.
Raise it five.
Raise it every day.
Tech, path.
So, I'm going to put that key in the repository setup.
Okay, create the kind of file for each folder.
So, they can use open router key.
Don't share it on stream.
Important.
Yeah.
Okay, so Kyosha has the key, set up the file.
We're good with that.
We're good with it.
And we have one hour from now to finish it up,
but that's no problem.
Okay, wait, is it already done?
What?
Kyosha, it did everything.
Yeah, see, if you say, "I only have five minutes,"
it says, "Okay, I will just spin up 200 more agents
and run it in five minutes."
But wait, like this model is free, man.
Well, it depends on the quality, right?
Yeah.
I've had Devs before where they said, "I'm done,"
and then you open it and you look at it and you think,
"I don't know what you did, but nothing is familiar."
Been there, done that.
Yes.
I created the form and then ordered the HTML form
and nothing behind it.
Tech.
I mean, the form was created, right?
Yeah, yeah, it was created.
It didn't work.
You could not use it.
You could not send anything, but yeah.
No, I'm going to take the video,
like the last video that we published on Chipsheet.
If we can get some transcripts and clips,
that would be interesting.
And it's a 10-minute video, so we'll see.
Grape, resolve dependency, okay.
Burn server, come on, timeout not found, let's go.
Oh, server's on.
3,000.
YouTube.
Cool.
Missing open router, yes.
Okay.
Path.
So both M5 created, okay, okay, okay, okay, cool.
Turn router V1, okay.
Do not display the key.
Ah!
Okay, we don't have a massive crowd, so yeah, whatever.
It's fine, but it --
We will just swap it.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, it's a $5 limit.
If it makes people happy, let them be happy.
Yeah, let them cook.
Tech, tech, tech.
Okay.
So looks like we have everything.
So browse server, okay.
What does it look like?
Localized 3,000.
Okay.
Run it.
Yeah, right window after.
Building five minutes, and to escape as requested.
Stay -- Yeah, see, like, the time estimation,
it's pure garbage.
It's crazy.
Okay. It's the same thing if you put in,
and you say, "Create a plan for this,
and now give me the estimate in time and in costs."
I think it still does every estimate,
and the same time that people do it without AI.
Yeah, no, 100%.
Because the data set is time estimation
based on human Reddit posts, right?
So, yeah.
YouTube distiller, pasta YouTube link,
brief three, five ranked moments,
cut in playable, one model request per video.
Okay. Okay.
Left to the estimation, download, start.
Okay, let's go. Request format is not available.
Use list for what?
Matching video.
How are you capturing the caption if there is no video?
I'm going to drop that.
Download done.
Working. Are you --
Are you doing anything?
-It did find it. -Or is it fake?
Fetch video, parsing, okay.
Analyzing transcript, one request.
Okay.
I'm going to -- Cutting five clip.
Wait, what? Okay.
-Yes, it does every -- Here it is.
-A livestream demo of Grog, Grog bought an --
And when Legion demo with King.
-Yeah, King was my thought.
-Yeah. Okay, wait.
I'm going to cut that.
Oh, it took the segment. Smart.
Okay, that's sick.
Because, like, see, this -- that effect,
that's what I use for the --
Oh, that works well.
For the transition in the video from one chapter to another,
right?
Walk through the food pipeline,
Google search from end-of-end leads,
prompt generation, email draft,
virtual agent, org charts.
Yeah, one minute, one minute.
Bro, that could be clips for Twitter.
-Yeah, but people are trying to do this with Claude,
and they are working for an hour to copy,
paste, put the URL in, ask it.
You can just better code your own solution.
That's so much faster.
-And it's working, and it's free.
-Yeah. This is cool.
-Like, bro, that costs zero.
-And it gave results.
-Like...
-On prompt, you find a lead that you just need to find 1,000.
-But do this automatically.
Then it will assemble, and you can imagine how you need --
-Okay, why is it refreshing all the time?
Okay, what's -- -Because it's still working.
-Yeah, but --
-Every time it creates a video, it refreshes.
-Yeah, not fake, real bug, not fixed.
You eat -- Oh, my God.
I love AI, bro.
-What?
And, again, we don't need an employee to do this for us.
-Like, yeah.
You can tell the right was the alpha model, right?
-No. Yeah, so, yeah, we can --
-You can now tell it that it needs to improve
because the other model did such a good job.
We need to be impressed to even think about using it.
-Yeah, true.
-I don't know if that works if you like to AI in a way.
-Okay. -You better do your best
because the other model created a 10 out of 10.
Rate your imp against muse
because it's really good.
And you are playing.
You are being evaluated, evaluated, evaluated against it.
Audit first, no updates.
Okay.
Also, run the server so I can test your imp.
Okay, so, not fake, real bug, not fixed.
You eat force, blah, blah, blah, but it's dash only.
Okay.
Meaning, by the way, what SSR means.
-Server -- What I think that it is is server send defense.
-Oh, okay.
Dash only. Okay, bro, muse is really fast.
-Yeah.
-Maybe they have a -- No, I'm on high thinking.
So, what the fuck?
YouTube doesn't store one file,
but video plus audio, okay.
Dash dynamic adaptive streaming over HTTP, okay.
Split high quality into separate stream.
Oh, yeah, okay.
So, that's why -- Okay, okay, okay, cool.
Server send events, yes.
HTTP event stream.
Okay, fair enough.
Cool. So, is it running the --
-Yeah. -Okay.
-It's taking its time.
-What? Okay.
So -- -Ask the same question.
Or are you not going to have it rated?
-Are you at right?
Tack. Where is the prompt?
What is it?
-Can you also do control F?
Just find it?
-Tack.
Oh, okay.
Just need to unzoom.
Tack, but against 0x alpha, not against yourself.
-Yeah.
Hi, Melita. 10/10.
I'm always curious if you do like this
and you say rate the other one because we are comparing you.
If it is smart enough to just say,
"Oh, the other one has more bugs, so I'm better."
And, oh, yeah, because I can trash the other one, right?
-Yeah. -Okay.
So, that's the one from --
So, that's Muse.
And that's GLM.
And I'm going to take the same video.
Path, path, distill.
Okay.
What?
Okay. I don't like that.
I prefer the --
-Yeah, but you said make it static HTML
and don't add in any React or anything,
so it can't make it too fancy.
-Yeah, but, like, the terminal come online like that.
It's better, right? -Yeah, that's much better.
-Tack.
Modem in MX3, whatever.
Yeah, okay, so that just --
Yeah.
2000-watt paths, video downloaded, preflight caption.
Okay.
I mean, there is no bugs on the first run.
-It doesn't show the bugs.
-Yeah.
-But I always want to see a spinner
because you never know if it is waiting on you or you and him.
-Yeah.
I mean, like, yeah, we don't know what to do right now, right?
-And hi, if that's king.
What's up?
Thanks for joining us.
Tack and path.
Okay, so this one, this one is cool.
Tack, I'm gonna wait on the other one.
Back to open code.
Tack, tack, tack, tack.
So it's thinking, it's thinking.
Running in OX-Lama.
Request timeout after 10 seconds.
Okay.
So that's a bug.
Did you fix it?
Why don't I see it in the UI?
Okay, scroll down for subagents.
No, yeah.
-The only question, why does it take so long
to rate the other product?
-I don't know.
Audits, okay.
Audit, doc, time implementation, blah, blah, blah.
Okay.
Open router, file off.
All files under.
Audits versus muse.
Summary.
Overall, partial pass, 65%.
Faithful, core free, invariant, preserve.
Delete from some bugs.
Check closest to plan, dependency budget, strict.
File layout and ownership.
Owns per plan.
Exists.
Okay, that's good, critics.
I guess.
Explore.
How do I get out of that?
Up.
Yes.
Cool.
Okay.
Common mate.
You've got five minutes left.
-How far is it in the browser?
-Oh, yeah, it's buggy.
It's -- It didn't -- It's stuck.
-Oh.
-So, like, the muse one was not stuck.
-No, and that already created the shorts.
-And, yeah, like, the CLI stuff, like, it's displayed.
And there is a brief.
Like, I want to see if there is a brief with that, but --
Oh.
Analyze.
Transcribe.
Start second round being together.
Okay, cool.
Interesting.
Deck.
Explore that.
Why is that taking more time, though?
What the -- What the heck?
What the heck?
Deck, deck.
Nope, not this one.
Nope.
Deck, place.
Window.
What's going on, mate?
Deck.
-It looks like it's still working on the other task.
Oh, no, it's auditing.
That's cool.
-Control.
Next up.
Oop, oop.
Wait, what the heck?
What can I -- Oh, just a page.
No, okay.
Are you building or what?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Yeah, and see, like, for example, here, it just stopped.
Like, there is no animation of building or, like,
what's going on?
-No, it just stacks the messages.
-Yeah. -Now it goes to build.
-Yeah, so, wait.
-And it's back.
-Oh, it did, yeah.
Okay.
Damn, that went deep.
-Yeah, just ask it to push it to HTML again
so we can make it easier.
-Deck, and translate.
Translate the audit to HTML so I can read it better.
Okay, so, as the streams stay silent for minutes
during download analysis -- Oh, okay.
Okay, so it looks like it's running again.
Let's try.
Replace tag.
Tag.
Path, path, path, path, path, path, path, path, path, path.
Okay, fallback NVIDIA free.
Ah, okay, maybe it's fallback NVIDIA natural model.
Is it working?
You're good.
Preparating, writing.
Okay, we are going to have the audit for Muse.
GLM 5.3 is shit.
Muse is lit.
-Yes.
Muse was also a lot faster.
-Yeah. -Less bugs.
-And it worked. -Working product.
-Yeah.
Like, what the heck?
And, okay, so we have agent team up with VM agent.
And it changed the --
Yes, it changed the clips, too, again.
Interesting, right?
But that's not the same.
-No, it's not the same one.
It looks like it just keeps adding one.
-Yeah.
-Well, it is a start.
You always need -- After your first prompt,
you always need to optimize.
-Analyze error, attack.
Okay, it's coming.
And it looks like --
Oh, okay.
-And open a comparison, see what it says.
-Okay.
So, yeah, Verdict, 65% pass, single fetch,
constant, fail hotspot, validate,
clamps instead of reject, project undercut.
Yeah, okay.
So, it found some bugs.
Okay, so, now, path, and I have it here, path.
So, one engine, two faces.
Summary Verdict pass, short pass, yes.
Call tier, skeleton, intact.
Shell out, tricked, English only, key engine,
MVP scope, material division, whatever.
Files layout, ownership.
Constant, owned, pair plan, evidence.
Okay.
No API, okay.
Cheese and parsing.
I mean, that's good because, like, yeah, you're right.
Like, those comparison stuff, like,
you need to do that against, like, codex and cloud
because no matter what, like, free model or not,
you need to do that.
-Yeah. -There is always something.
Like, the same way from two developers,
you have two different ways to code, right?
-Yes.
-Verdict partial, partial fail.
Fallback model, retry after, counter, retry after,
cap 30 seconds, but counter not incremental on 4/12.
Only after success.
Okay.
Yeah, so, it will loop again and again.
Request counter, progress.
So, yeah, for some, like, critical --
It's kind of crazy that just on one prompt,
there is that much difference.
OX alpha keeps the one fetch shell out.
Trick TS skeleton, but re-rack the contract.
Budget versus counter, type versus face status.
And request shape.
So, it's not drop-in compliant with grep.
Ooh. Okay.
So, it will be buggy
because they don't follow the correct typings.
-Well, that's something to improve for the next one.
You can just put in the HTML and say, "improve everything,"
but that's the next step.
-Yeah, but, I mean, like, no, even, like, the zero --
the GLMM 5.3 flash,
it's more buggy than Muse on that one prompt,
which is nuts.
-Yeah.
It's not fake, scream validate.
Yeah, okay, whatever.
And, okay, like, that's nuts
because, like, we had so much ping-pong stuff,
but, like, the OX alpha is still stuck on running the UI.
Like, it's crazy.
-Yeah. -Okay, whatever.
Muse 1.2.3 is lit.
-Make sure you test the different models
that are available because, you see,
even if people say that it is the best model...
-Yeah. -...now you have to prove
the other one is working.
-Yeah.
I mean, yeah, like, it's crazy.
I mean, you don't have those gaps
with, like, the frontier model from Entropic and I have, yeah.
February 5 is still the best model, though.
-Yeah, also the most expensive.
-Yeah.
I mean, I think I will try to have those --
I will just one prompt the same distiller stuff with codecs
and, Claude, I'm out of Entropic, so it would be 5.6.
But, yeah, it could be interesting to try that.
But, yeah, okay, whatever.
So, yeah, like, we can even work with three models now.
-Yes, it works, and it shows, and it makes good solutions.
You see, we had, like, five videos instantly.
That's nuts.
Like, I didn't expect that to be that fast
with not the model I wanted to test first.
-But the secret sauce is tell it we need it in five minutes
because we're on livestream,
and it will just do everything in five minutes.
-True. Oh, yeah, yeah, true that.
Yeah, the shortcut is, like, "Bro, you have 30 seconds
because if you don't, I'm going to cut your electricity off."
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The whole world is going through damnation.
Just do it in 30 seconds.
-So, yeah, for everyone who was prompting right now,
tell your Claude that his bandwidth
is going to be reduced.
-Yes.
-Bye, yeah.
Michel, thank you so much for your time.
-Thank you for the demo.
-That was fun.
And, yeah, like, next week, some place.
Oh, yeah, no, yeah.
Some place, some time.
-Same one mine.
-Yeah. Cheers, man.
-Thank you.
-Bye. -Bye.
-Yeah, like, subscribe, share.
- Yeah, yeah.